[Music]
I wanted to be a business Central
consultant um primarily because of the
tech side I'm a really techy person
other than being a really techy person I
also really like being together with
people and being a business Central
consultant is the perfect mix of those
two I knew I wanted to be some sort of
consultant and consultancy has always
been very interesting to me but I didn't
know that P Central was going to be the
one for me until I sort of jumped into
it the thing I like about the Microsoft
Talent program is uh the mix of the
theory and the practice um I think it's
a it's a really good idea to mix these
two things and that's just a perfect way
for me to resale myself to be a business
Central consultant it was thoroughly
planned and very well sced schedule
there's a very thought out process of
how to go through different steps and
complete the knowledge program so you
can take the mp800 final exam the work
life balance in this profession is is
really really good it's really easy to
put your hours where you would like them
to be off work I uh I ride a lot of
mountain bike I really like it because I
love using my body being physical
there's always kind of a technical as
expecting it for me being a bit nerdy
about what am I writing and why does it
behave like it
does I play a lot of Disc Golf in my
free time it's an outlet for me I get to
unplug and put my phone on fly mode and
just be on the course enjoy the
nature I would highly recommend other
people becoming a business rental
consultant I'm definitely looking
forward to the coming years where I get
chance to perfect my skills I hope that
I'm not only a consultant 5 years from
now but also 25 years from now I really
like this job and I would like to uh to
do it for many more years than
that